Thomas Dominguez

Full Stack Developer

(+54) 91159705599, Thomas41392@gmail.com, Portfolio

I am a Full Stack Developer with more than 1 year of experience in web and mobile development. My knowledge includes HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Node.js, and databases like MySQL and PostgreSQL. I also have experience in responsive design, Scrum methodologies, and problem solving skills, effective communication, and teamwork. I speak English at C1 level and Italian A2.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE / PROJECTS

Full Stack Developer

Freelance.

Feb 2023 - Apr 2023.

Develop online expense management software/application using React, Node, Aws. Design interfaces and frontend elements, maintain and optimize website and interfaces.

Front End Mobile Developer - Go rent

Nov. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Academic experience.

No country, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Technologies: React native, Node Js, Express, PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

Link al repo

Fullstack Web Developer - Shoes e-commerce

June 2022 - July 2022

Academic experience.

Henry, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Technologies:: React native, Node Js, Express, PostgreSQL v Sequelize.

Link al repo

TECHNOLOGIES

Idioms: Javascript, Typescript

Frameworks: React, Node, React Native, Redux, Express, Sequelize

Database: Postgresql, Mysql, Firebase.

Others: Git, Jira, Slack, Figma, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Css, HTML, Scrum.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer. Henry - 2022.

Argentina program.2022.

Introduction to Java. udemy.2021.

HTML, CSS and JavaScript course. SoloLearn.2021.

Communications oriented secondary -2016.

EF SET English Certified 62/100 (C1 advanced).

Italiano A2 busin